Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/anh-nguyen-95b37436 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

User Journeys
Site Maps
Communication

Anh Nguyen

Product Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

My name is Nguyen Duc Anh. I'm an UX/UI and Product Designer from Ho Chi Minh City.

I have more than 7 years of experience working on UX/UI Design and 3 years working as Lead Art at C-Smile Magazine. I love everything that has to do with Apps design & development. I also want to work with something relate to Graphic design and Packaging.

I love to create the designs that look fresh, inspiration, creative, passion, unique and usable.

Experience

Freelance
Product Designer
February 2015 - Present (10 years 2 months)

RMIT International University Vietnam Student

GalaxyOne
3 years 6 months

UX Manager February 2022 - Present (3 years 2 months)

Senior Product Designer October 2021 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Freelance App and Web designer UX/UI Designer August 2013 - Present (11 years 8 months) Vietnam

Vietsunshine Electronic Solution Joint Stock Company UX/UI Lead

October 2018 - October 2021 (3 years 1 month)

Vietnam

ZAMO

Freelance UX/UI Designer November 2016 - November 2018 (2 years 1 month) Vietnam

goGame, a subsidiary of SEGA UX/UI Designer January 2016 - October 2018 (2 years 10 months) Vietnam

CSmile Magazine Lead Artist February 2012 - August 2015 (3 years 7 months) Vietnam

Education

RMIT University Vietnam

Bachelor's degree, Multimedia Design · (2011 - 2014)